<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[First Class Concierge Services]]></title><description><![CDATA[At First Class Concierge Services, we know your time is precious, which is why we provide our clients with bespoke lifestyle assistance.]]></description><link>https://www.firstclass-concierge.com/blog</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 13:27:13 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.firstclass-concierge.com/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[Hiking in UAE: The Rainbow Valley, Wadi Ghub, Fujairah]]></title><description><![CDATA[With the start of October month, the weather starts to be much more cooler and allow you to explore much more the natural beauties of the...]]></description><link>https://www.firstclass-concierge.com/post/hiking-in-uae-the-rainbow-valley-wadi-ghub-fujairah</link><guid isPermaLink="false">634529f5cc6e2d4012fe60c9</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2022 05:48:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_c66c6f08aa684c45b2b06e9fa2f6bb6a~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Matteo Viganò</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>With the start of October month, the weather starts to be much more cooler and allow you to explore much more the natural beauties of the Seven Emirates. </p>
<p>Hiking, camping and a nice BBQ for your week-end is definitely the best solution if you are into outdoors activities from this month onwards, then let's start with a great location not too far from the busy Dubai: Wadi Ghub, called The Rainbow Valley. The starting of the hike is located about 2 hours from Dubai, in the Fujairah Emirates direction to Dibba. I suggest to leave the city quite early ignorer to be at the starting point around 6:30 am and have all the time to enjoy the hike before the sun is covering the path and makes the walk very difficult.</p>
<p>The full loop is about 15 km, however you can as well try to reach the Spectrum area, the highlight of the hike with its colorful rocks and come back to the starting point making about 5 km and a good exercise for beginners.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_c66c6f08aa684c45b2b06e9fa2f6bb6a~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_5d55d901a40540cb949239c475dce303~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_786,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_77451ddfdb984a64a9b0d0b73a1647aa~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_aeaea9618d7e47b58668e14c72f3a3df~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>After the hike, you will have the rest of the day to relax on the beach and enjoy the clear waters of Snoopy Island located about 30 minutes from Wadi Ghub. The island is right in front of the Sandy Beach Resort <a href="(https://sandybeach.ae)" target="_blank" ><u>(https://sandybeach.ae)</u></a> and where if you are interested you can rent the snorkeling equipment and see some turtles and if lucky smell sharks as well! Not in the mood for resort? No issues, just beside the hotel a free public beach is available and you can set up your tent, BBQ and spend the night looking at the stars.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_8ace719a8c9b4a64965dac0af4b76903~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_879,h_744,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Island Escape: Anantara World Island Resort]]></title><description><![CDATA[The recently opened Anantara World Islands resort is one of the best location to fulfill your relax wishes. It is a perfect hotel for...]]></description><link>https://www.firstclass-concierge.com/post/island-escape-anantara-world-island-resort</link><guid isPermaLink="false">632d894ee734ea972c9be918</guid><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 10:44:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_324eecc877a4429fb3e8fd1110154d3c~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Matteo Viganò</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The recently opened Anantara World Islands resort is one of the best location to fulfill your relax wishes. </p>
<p>It is a perfect hotel for those who are looking for something different in Dubai or for returning guests that tried already whatever Dubai can offer. An oasis of peace, just 25 minutes by boat from the sister property Anantara Palm Resort that can wow you with pristine beaches, fabulous suites and rooms and an amazing Indian-inspired restaurant: Qamar. </p>
<p>Pamper yourself with a night away from the busy Dubai in a paradise corner facing Burj Khalifa and Downtown skyline, or simply visit the island for a day pass to the extraordinary.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_324eecc877a4429fb3e8fd1110154d3c~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><a href="https://video.wixstatic.com/video/211a07_c2f70ca0d7e6496caa1dd8204018e5da/480p/mp4/file.mp4">https://video.wixstatic.com/video/211a07_c2f70ca0d7e6496caa1dd8204018e5da/480p/mp4/file.mp4</a><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_249c7678276a42a79903e435f8a78dff~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_0d8cdfc90ff646988a5be658eaf0f1bd~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New cool spot in the City: Dubai Harbour]]></title><description><![CDATA[The new lively area is getting famous in town!]]></description><link>https://www.firstclass-concierge.com/post/newcoolspotinthecity-dubaiharbour</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63295285c946b5ccd983d56d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 05:41:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_5935fe015d864aad9795442969e31e51~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Matteo Viganò</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In the heart of the city, the newly opened Dubai Yacht Harbour is a quiet spot where new residences, restaurants and projects will take place soon before the winter season.</p>

<p>Located near Dubai Marina, the new area hosts all the modern facilities to dock yachts and international cruises taking the place of the old Mena Port in Jumeirah 1 Area. The EMAAR developer as well handed over recently some of the most beautiful residencies at the very end of the Marina with a wonderful view of the Arabian Gulf, as well new hotels are going to open in the same location and one of the example is the W Hotel, Mina Seyahi.</p>

<p>Whatever you are going to reach by yacht or from the city, Dubai Harbour gives you a chance to enjoy the flavors of south of Italy at <strong><em>L'Amo Bistro del Mare restaurant</em></strong>: a real pearl with its refined menu mainly based on fresh seafood and pasta. The venue has a fine design and light interior colors to recall the blue of the sea and Dubai sky, while the outdoor terrace has a stunning view of the harbour enjoyable all day long. </p>
<p>Tip: the freshly made Cacio and Pepe Spaghettoni pasta is simply delicious! </p>
<p><a href="https://lamorestaurant.com" target="_blank" ><u>https://lamorestaurant.com</u></a> </p>

<p>And why not? Fancy a drink after dinner? the area can offer you more and more with <strong><em>Bar Du Port:</em></strong> busy bar lounge where the entertainment never stops and lively al fresco Happy Hours are served daily. <a href="https://www.barduportdubai.com" target="_blank" ><u>https://www.barduportdubai.com</u></a>  </p>

<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/211a07_50788f9d9cf6422fa936cabfc5ccbe70~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>#dubaiharbour #luxuryhospitality #dubaitoursim</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>